https://www.stjeans.com/privacy-policy/

St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. Any personally identifiable information about you is considered personal information and will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy.Personal information means information about an identifiable individual, such as name, home mailing address, home phone number, and employment information.St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. collects, uses and discloses personal information for the following purposes:Maintaining a customer mailing list for our mail-order business;Processing and recording sales transactions for goods and services provided;Maintaining customer sales history for after-sales service;Notifying you of certain products or services that may be of interest to you;Compiling statistics for our own purposes;To verify credit worthiness;To manage an employee relationship.We rely on the following actions by you as indications of your consent to our personal information practices:Your voluntary provision of personal information to St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd.Your express consent or acknowledgement contained within a written, verbal or electronic application processYour consent solicited by St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. for a specified purposeYou may withhold or withdraw this consent at any time. Your decision to withhold or withdraw your consent, may restrict our ability to provide a particular service or product. If so, we will explain the situation to assist you in making the decision.We may collect, use or disclose personal information without your knowledge or consent in the following limited circumstances:When the collection, use or disclosure of personal information is permitted or required by law;In an emergency that threatens an individual’s life, health or personal security;For the purposes of collecting a debt;To protect ourselves from fraud.St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. will only collect, use or disclose personal information that is necessary for the identified purposes. We will retain personal information only as long as required.St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. will maintain your personal information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is possible.St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd. has designated a Privacy Officer who is accountable to the owner of the corporation for compliance with this privacy policy. You should direct any concerns or questions regarding St. Jean’s Cannery Ltd.’s compliance with this policy in writing to the Privacy Officer. If the Privacy Officer is unable to resolve the concern, you may contact the Information and Privacy Commissioner of British Columbia.If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Officer at 1-866-754-3191.
closeAbout UsHistory of St. Jean’s Cannery & SmokehouseFAQCo-Pack and Private LabelInternational CustomersMedia VideosCovid-19 Safety PlanSport FishingGetting Your Fish to St. Jean’sSport Fishing Order InquirySport Processing RatesSport Fishing LodgesRecipesContact UsShipping & ReturnsTop Rated Products
Canned Tuna No Salt | 150g			Rated 5.00 out of 5 $5.95 – $68.00
Canned Wild Sockeye Salmon | 105g			Rated 5.00 out of 5 $5.95 – $65.00
Large Wooden Gift Box | Salmon			Rated 5.00 out of 5 $119.95
Search											MenuCategoriesCannedWild Pacific SalmonWild Albacore TunaShellfishPacific Smoked OystersSmoked Salt Spring Island MusselsOyster & Clam ChowdersButter Clams & NectarSauces & SpicesRaincoast MarinadeCajun Spice BlendAntipasto & Red Pepper JellyFrozenHot SmokedHot Smoked Wild SalmonHot Smoked Albacore TunaPeppercorn Smoked Wild SalmonCandiedCandied Wild SalmonCandied Albacore TunaCandied Peppercorn Wild SalmonCold Smoked (Lox)Wild Salmon | Presliced LoxAlbacore Tuna | Presliced LoxFillets & PrawnsWild Sockeye Salmon SidesHalibut FilletsBlack Cod FilletsWild BC Spot Prawns (Shell On)GiftsNEW Gift TinsGift BasketsGift BoxesAssortmentsPet FoodFor CatsFor DogsLimited IngredientsTreatsAbout UsHistory of St. Jean’s Cannery & SmokehouseSport FishingSport Processing RatesSport Fishing Order InquirySport Fishing LodgesGetting Your Fish to St. Jean’sFAQCo-Pack and Private LabelMedia VideosRecipesInternational CustomersShipping & ReturnsCanned Dry GoodsWild Pacific SalmonWild Albacore TunaClams, Oysters & MusselsSauces, Spices, & PateFrozen SeafoodCandiedFillets & PrawnsCold Smoked (Lox)Hot SmokedGift IdeasGift BoxesGift BasketsGift TinsAssortmentsPet FoodContact UsLogin / RegisterShopping cart
closeSign in
close
Username or email *
Password *
Log in
Lost your password?
Remember me
No account yet?
Create an Account
Sidebar
Scroll To Top
We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing this website, you agree to our use of cookies. To add products to your cart, cookies must be turned on.
More info
Accept
